Guide to the Ella Winter Papers
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series VII: Printed Material
  - By Ella Winter (Box 31)
  - About Ella Winter (Box 31)
  - Pete Steffens (Box 31)
  - Donald Ogden Stewart (Box 31)
  - Brochures and Circulars (Box 31)
  - Annotated and miscellaneous (Box 31)